{
  "name": "Kardashians",
  "color": [171,141,77],
  "questions":
  [
    {
      "question": "Who is The Momager",
      "answers": ["Kris","Katelyn","Kim","Kylie"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who got the Noms?",
      "answers": ["Khloe","Kylie","Kim","Kourtney"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who got arrested for DUI?",
      "answers": ["Khloe","Kourtney","Kim","Kris"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Kris's son's name?",
      "answers": ["Rob","Bob","Kevin","Kyle"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who sings Jingle Bells?",
      "answers": ["Kris","Khloe","Kim","Kourtney"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Joyce Byers?",
      "answers": ["Will's Mom","Barb's Mom", "Max's Mom","Mike's Mom"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is North's Mom?",
      "answers": ["Kim","Khloe","Kourtney","Kylie"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the Oldest Sister?",
      "answers": ["Kourtney","Khloe","Kim","Kylie"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is The Yongest Sister?",
      "answers": ["Kylie","Kendall","Kim","Khloe"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who had stole Kim's wedding country?",
      "answers": ["Kourtney","Kris","Katelyn","Khloe"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who lost her earring in the ocean?",
      "answers": ["Kim","Kylie","Kris","Khloe"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said 'Kim, there's people dying'?",
      "answers": ["Kourtney","Kylie","Kris","Khloe"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many grandchildren does Kris have?",
      "answers": ["12","14","10","16"],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
}